Somebody got shot!
किसी को गोली लग गई!
Boys, come here. Y'all boys come here! Come here!
लड़कों, इधर आओ। सब लड़के इधर आओ! इधर आओ!
-You sure she got shot? -Yes!
-तुम्हें यकीन है कि उसे गोली लगी है? -हाँ!
Oh my God! Why did she do this?
हे भगवान! उसने ऐसा क्यों किया?
But from my understanding, everybody, all the kids,
लेकिन मेरी समझ से, हर कोई, सभी बच्चे,
has problems with this lady.
इस महिला के साथ समस्या है.
I called because the lady across the street on the phone hit me with a sign.
मैंने फोन इसलिए किया क्योंकि सड़क के उस पार वाली महिला ने मुझे फोन पर एक संकेत दिया था।
Her children were walking their dog on the property.
उसके बच्चे अपने कुत्ते को संपत्ति पर घुमाने ले जा रहे थे।
It clearly says, "No Trespassing."
इसमें स्पष्ट रूप से लिखा है, "अतिक्रमण निषेध।"
And they're always walking the dog.
और वे हमेशा कुत्ते को टहलाते रहते हैं।
The dog's always taking a crap.
कुत्ता हमेशा मल त्याग करता रहता है।
There's poop on the sidewalk. All kinds of stuff.
फुटपाथ पर मल-मूत्र पड़ा है। हर तरह की चीज़ें।
I said, "Can you keep the dog over there?"
मैंने कहा, "क्या आप कुत्ते को वहां रख सकते हैं?"
I was going to take a picture of her dog
मैं उसके कुत्ते की तस्वीर लेने जा रहा था
and she said, "Don't take a picture of my children."
और उसने कहा, "मेरे बच्चों की तस्वीर मत लो।"
And I'm like, "Nah."
और मैं कहता हूं, "नहीं।"
And then she just got in my face
और फिर वह मेरे चेहरे पर आ गई
and she picked up the sign and threw it at me.
और उसने वह तख्ती उठाकर मेरी ओर फेंक दी।
And it hit me in the leg.
और वह मेरे पैर में लगी।
It's harassing people, like,
यह लोगों को परेशान कर रहा है, जैसे,
you don't own this.
यह आपका नहीं है.
You can't tell people…
आप लोगों को यह नहीं बता सकते...
Lots of children screaming their fool heads off,
बहुत सारे बच्चे जोर-जोर से चिल्ला रहे हैं,
running around.
इधर उधर भागते हुए.
I had my truck parked in front of here,
मैंने अपना ट्रक यहाँ सामने खड़ा किया था,
so I didn't have to listen to the screaming and yelling.
इसलिए मुझे चीखने-चिल्लाने की आवाजें सुनने की जरूरत नहीं पड़ी ।
As soon as I moved the truck, the kids are coming up.
जैसे ही मैंने ट्रक को आगे बढ़ाया, बच्चे ऊपर आ गए।
I'm like, guys, stop.
मैं कहता हूं, दोस्तों, रुको।
They know they're not supposed to be here. They've been told a million times.
उन्हें पता है कि उन्हें यहाँ नहीं होना चाहिए । उन्हें लाखों बार कहा जा चुका है।
And the little kid tells me to shut up to my face.
और वह छोटा बच्चा मेरे मुंह पर ही मुझे चुप रहने को कहता है।
I said, "Don't be disrespectful to me."
मैंने कहा, "मेरे प्रति अनादर मत करो।"
And he's exchanging words back and forth.
और वह एक दूसरे से बातें कर रहा है।
I'm like, "Listen, my name is Dr. Lorincz. Don't tell me to shut up."
मैंने कहा, "सुनो, मेरा नाम डॉ. लोरिन्ज़ है। मुझे चुप रहने के लिए मत कहो।"
And he was calling me names and I'm like,
और वह मुझे गालियाँ दे रहा था और मैं ऐसा था,
no, no, no, we're not going to do that.
नहीं, नहीं, नहीं, हम ऐसा नहीं करने जा रहे हैं।
I took my son to question the one whose face that she was in.
मैं अपने बेटे को उस व्यक्ति से पूछताछ करने के लिए ले गया जिसका चेहरा उस पर था।
Then she got an air horn.
फिर उसे एक एयर हॉर्न मिला।
And I mean, she gunned her engine so hard.
और मेरा मतलब है, उसने अपना इंजन बहुत जोर से चलाया।
I swear, I thought one of these kids was hit.
मैं कसम खाता हूँ, मुझे लगा कि इनमें से एक बच्चा मारा गया था।
I swear.
मैं कसम खाता हूँ।
And she just kept on flying out the neighborhood.
और वह बस पड़ोस से बाहर उड़ती रही।
I'm sorry, I panicked.
मुझे खेद है, मैं घबरा गया।
And then the guy locked me in there, I thought…
और फिर उस आदमी ने मुझे वहाँ बंद कर दिया, मैंने सोचा...
I'm sorry. I've been previously raped and beaten.
मुझे माफ़ करना। मेरे साथ पहले भी बलात्कार और मारपीट हो चुकी है।
And so I panicked.
और इसलिए मैं घबरा गया।
I mean, I really panicked.
मेरा मतलब है, मैं सचमुच घबरा गया।
And then I thought I was in trouble.
और फिर मुझे लगा कि मैं मुसीबत में हूं।
Like, I thought someone was going to harm me.
जैसे, मुझे लगा कि कोई मुझे नुकसान पहुँचाने वाला है।
We're gonna take off, but can you guys just do me a favor?
हम लोग उड़ान भरने जा रहे हैं, लेकिन क्या आप लोग मुझ पर एक एहसान कर सकते हैं?
Just keep an eye on your kids and make sure they don't go over there?
बस अपने बच्चों पर नज़र रखें और सुनिश्चित करें कि वे वहाँ न जाएँ?
Because I think we all appreciate not getting a bunch of calls
क्योंकि मुझे लगता है कि हम सभी को ढेर सारे कॉल न आने की खुशी है
to come over here over and over about nothing.
यहाँ बार-बार बिना किसी कारण के आना ।
They just keep… They're trespassing, trespassing.
वे बस... वे अतिक्रमण कर रहे हैं, अतिक्रमण कर रहे हैं।
Called an officer out last night, nobody shows up.
कल रात एक अधिकारी को बुलाया, कोई नहीं आया।
I guess the mother of the children may have interceded.
मुझे लगता है कि बच्चों की माँ ने बीच-बचाव किया होगा।
She was out there waiting.
वह बाहर इंतज़ार कर रही थी।
I mean, I just have the burnt sign that they threw.
मेरा मतलब है, मेरे पास बस वह जला हुआ साइन है जो उन्होंने फेंका था।
I'm like, all right, you're sending me a message.
मैं कहता हूं, ठीक है, आप मुझे संदेश भेज रहे हैं।
Thank you so much.
आपका बहुत-बहुत धन्यवाद।
I like being honest with everybody
मुझे सबके साथ ईमानदार रहना पसंद है
so they know exactly what's set down and done for them.
ताकि उन्हें ठीक-ठीक पता रहे कि उनके लिए क्या निर्धारित किया गया है और क्या किया गया है।
This is basically just gonna be an official police document
यह मूलतः एक आधिकारिक पुलिस दस्तावेज़ होगा
because you don't have video proof…
क्योंकि आपके पास वीडियो सबूत नहीं है...
I know.
मुझे पता है।
…of the arson and the criminal mischief.
... आगजनी और आपराधिक शरारत की।
So it will just be a police document, more or less.
तो यह कमोबेश एक पुलिस दस्तावेज ही होगा ।
We got kids trespassing, standing there, leaving all the toys around,
हमने बच्चों को अतिक्रमण करते हुए देखा, जो वहां खड़े थे और सारे खिलौने इधर-उधर छोड़ गए थे,
just screaming, yelling, just being absolutely obnoxious.
बस चीखना, चिल्लाना, बिल्कुल अप्रिय व्यवहार करना।
I went and threw the roller skates over to the other side.
मैं गया और रोलर स्केट्स को दूसरी तरफ फेंक दिया।
The kid says, "I'm going to beat you up for that."
बच्चा कहता है, "मैं इसके लिए तुम्हें पीटूंगा।"
Yeah, there are several kids out there now.
हाँ, अब वहाँ कई बच्चे हैं।
I'm fearing for my life.
मुझे अपनी जान का डर सता रहा है।
I'm very scared.
मैं बहुत भयभीत हूं।
No.
नहीं।
And the kid's saying I took his iPad
और बच्चा कह रहा है कि मैंने उसका आईपैड ले लिया
and all this other shady shit that isn't true.
और ये सब अन्य छायादार बकवास जो सच नहीं है।
I don't like the kids threatening me that they'll beat me up,
मुझे यह पसंद नहीं कि बच्चे मुझे धमकी दें कि वे मुझे पीटेंगे।
that they're going to get someone else to kill me.
कि वे मुझे मारने के लिए किसी और को लाएंगे ।
This is just ridiculous.
यह तो हास्यास्पद है.
They just keep badgering me and badgering me.
वे बस मुझे परेशान करते रहते हैं ।
I'm just sick of these children.
मैं इन बच्चों से तंग आ गया हूं।
Now that they're home from school, it's like, you know,
अब जब वे स्कूल से घर आ गए हैं, तो ऐसा है, आप जानते हैं,
craziness.
पागलपन.
Please. Yes.
कृपया, हाँ।
Because what's going to happen is,
क्योंकि जो होने वाला है,
his mom's gonna go and wait for the officer,
उसकी माँ जाकर अधिकारी का इंतज़ार करेगी,
and run and say, "Oh my God," I was threatening her kid.
और दौड़कर कहो, "हे भगवान," मैं उसके बच्चे को धमकी दे रहा था।
Which just isn't true.
जो कि सच नहीं है।
Okay, thanks.
ठीक है, धन्यवाद.
Call 911!
911 पर कॉल करें!
Hey, call 911!
अरे, 911 पर कॉल करो!
Please!
कृपया!
She shot my mom!
उसने मेरी माँ को गोली मार दी!
-Who shot your mom? -The Karen!
-तुम्हारी माँ को किसने गोली मारी? -करेन!
With a freaking gun!
एक भयानक बंदूक के साथ!
Oh my God, this lady just tried to break down my door.
हे भगवान, इस महिला ने अभी-अभी मेरा दरवाजा तोड़ने की कोशिश की।
I shot through the door.
मैंने दरवाज़े से गोली चलाई.
Oh my God!
अरे बाप रे!
Susan Lorincz.
सुसान लोरिन्ज़.
I didn't know what to do. I grabbed my gun and I shot at the door
मुझे समझ नहीं आ रहा था कि क्या करूँ। मैंने अपनी बंदूक उठाई और दरवाज़े पर गोली चला दी।
and I thought she was gonna kill me.
और मुझे लगा कि वह मुझे मार डालेगी।
Yes. She's come after me several times
हाँ। वह कई बार मेरे पीछे आई है।
because of her children, her children keep trespassing over here.
उसके बच्चों की वजह से, उसके बच्चे यहाँ पर अतिक्रमण करते रहते हैं।
They're bothering me and bothering me. They won't fucking stop.
वे मुझे परेशान कर रहे हैं, परेशान कर रहे हैं। वे रुकने वाले नहीं हैं।
Her boys were here earlier.
उसके लड़के पहले यहाँ आये थे।
They keep leaving their garbage all around the house.
वे अपना कचरा घर में इधर-उधर छोड़ते रहते हैं।
And then I told them to take the crap away,
और फिर मैंने उनसे कहा कि वे यह बकवास हटा दें,
get the fuck outta here.
यहां से चले जाओ.
I'd like him to close the door. I have two cats inside.
मैं चाहता हूँ कि वह दरवाज़ा बंद कर दे। अंदर मेरी दो बिल्लियाँ हैं।
Why would you shoot her?
तुम उसे गोली क्यों मारोगे?
I'm gonna tell them. I'll tell them.
मैं उन्हें बताऊँगा। मैं उन्हें बताऊँगा।
I'm sorry, Isaac.
मुझे खेद है, इसहाक.
Football. That's what they play over there. Football.
फ़ुटबॉल। वहाँ यही खेलते हैं। फ़ुटबॉल।
All right, Susan, I put all those items in your purse, okay?
ठीक है, सुसान, मैंने वे सभी चीजें तुम्हारे पर्स में रख दीं, ठीक है?
They're on the hood of the car.
वे कार के हुड पर हैं।
Again, we're just trying to make sure you're safe and everything.
पुनः, हम केवल यह सुनिश्चित करने का प्रयास कर रहे हैं कि आप सुरक्षित रहें और सब कुछ ठीक रहे।
-Understood. -But just please call…
-समझ गया। -लेकिन कृपया फ़ोन कर लो...
Yeah, this doesn't mean they get to break her shit.
हाँ, इसका मतलब यह नहीं है कि वे उसकी चीज़ें तोड़ देंगे।